{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which Greek letter represents the &quot;Half-Life&quot; logo?","correct_answer":"Lambda","incorrect_answers":["Omega","Alpha","Sigma"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who&#039;s the voice actor for Thrall in the Warcraft game series?","correct_answer":"Chris Metzen","incorrect_answers":["Ben Affleck","Jason Derulo","Jim Carrey"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which of these is a type of monster found in Minecraft?","correct_answer":"Skeleton","incorrect_answers":["Werewolf","Vampire","Minotaur"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What is Pikachu&#039;s National Pok&eacute;Dex Number?","correct_answer":"#025","incorrect_answers":["#001","#031","#109"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the game Dark Souls, what is the name of the region you&#039;re in for the majority of the game?","correct_answer":"Lordran","incorrect_answers":["Drangleic","Oolacile","Catarina"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What&#039;s the Team Fortress 2 Scout&#039;s city of origin?","correct_answer":"Boston","incorrect_answers":["Sydney","Detroit","New York"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which of these is NOT a playable character in &quot;Left 4 Dead&quot;?","correct_answer":"Nick","incorrect_answers":["Louis","Zoey","Bill"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who is the leader of Team Valor in Pok&eacute;mon Go?","correct_answer":"Candela","incorrect_answers":["Willow","Blanche","Spark"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"How many differently shaped Tetris pieces are there?","correct_answer":"7","incorrect_answers":["5","6","8"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In what year was Hearthstone released?","correct_answer":"2014","incorrect_answers":["2011","2013","2012"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who are the original creators of Rachet &amp; Clank?","correct_answer":"Insomniac Games","incorrect_answers":["PixelTail Games","Rare","Bethesda"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"The name of the Metroid series comes from what?","correct_answer":"An enemy in the game","incorrect_answers":["The final boss&#039;s name","The main character&#039;s name","A spaceship&#039;s name"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What video game engine does the videogame Quake 2 run in?","correct_answer":"iD Tech 2","incorrect_answers":["iD Tech 3","iD Tech 1","Unreal Engine"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What game was used to advertise Steam?","correct_answer":"Counter-Strike 1.6","incorrect_answers":["Half-Life","Half-Life 2","Team Fortress"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What is the name of the City in Saints Row The Third?","correct_answer":"Steelport","incorrect_answers":["Stilwater","Carcer","Liberty"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What are Sans and Papyrus named after in &quot;Undertale&quot;?","correct_answer":"Fonts","incorrect_answers":["Plants","Companies","Ancient writing paper"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the original Spyro game who is the first villain?","correct_answer":"Gnasty Gnorc","incorrect_answers":["Ripto","Sorceress","Cynder"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In Splatoon 2, who are the members of Off The Hook?","correct_answer":"Pearl &amp; Marina","incorrect_answers":["Callie &amp; Marie","Diamond &amp; Aquamarina","DJ Octavio &amp; Crusty Sean"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"How many obsidian blocks are required to build a nether portal in Minecraft?","correct_answer":"10","incorrect_answers":["14","13","16"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the video game &quot;Postal 2&quot;, what is the name of Postal Dude&#039;s dog?","correct_answer":"Champ","incorrect_answers":["Snoopy","Krotchy","Duke"]}]}
